playgame.net 2010-11-21

# Play Game , Privacy

## Privacy

  * This contract Playgame.net and connected to all users who use the service covers. 
  * **Use of Personal Information**  
User's personal information to third parties or organizations are not by us. For example, we have provided the name, last name, such as e-mail address information is not sold to other firms. 
  * **On the Use of Personal Information**  
Playgame.net users any information you enter during registration or later only in the framework of legal cases and legal procedures open to third parties. This legal situation can occur are in substance the following condition;   
a) a written request in this direction consists of the legal authorities in the case of   
b) Playgame.net to protect and defend the property rights to   
c) The rules adopted under conditions of use   

  * **Personal information will be shared Guarantee**  
Playgame.net the registered user information privacy that the contract in any way with the exception of substances, can not be distributed, duplicated, can not be sold or shared with third parties. In this Convention undertake all measures Playgame.net to receive guarantees. 
  * **Correction of personal information, to Update and Delete**  
Playgame.net record of its own as each user has the right to change any information. Users can access their own officials if Playgame the deletion may provide any information. 
  * **Security Measures**  
You must have an antivirus program on your computer, and absolutely needs to be updated periodically with. Via mail or MSN open files from people you do not know you should not. 
  * Corporate blogs are not reliable and not shown on site do not give your email address. 
  * Difficult to guess your password, you must be careful to create a combination. Be easy to guess the birth date, favorite artists, like the football team should not put the passwords are encrypted this way can be easily captured. 
  * **Copyright**  
Playgame.net in the game, video, joke, picture content, such as any of you think this violates your copyright, please contact us at the nearest time the content will be removed from our site. 
  * For questions and suggestions: **help@playgame.net**
